[
    {
        "question": "Which European city is nicknamed `The Eternal City`?",
        "answer": "Rome"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what Australian state would you find Armidale?",
        "answer": "New South Wales"
    },
    {
        "question": "Libreville is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Gabon"
    },
    {
        "question": "Libreville is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Gabon"
    },
    {
        "question": "What currency is dispensed from Antarctica`s only ATM?",
        "answer": "U.S. dollar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which mountain range is home to the snow leopard?",
        "answer": "Himalayas"
    },
    {
        "question": "Rome, which animal is protected under the law?",
        "answer": "Cat"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the state animal for the U.S. state Florida?",
        "answer": "Florida panther"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country are the Plitvice Lakes located?",
        "answer": "Croatia"
    },
    {
        "question": "The world`s smallest bat is native to which two countries?",
        "answer": "Thailand and Myanmar -- Kitti`s Hog-Nosed Bat, more commonly known as the Bumblebee Bat, is 1.5 inches long and weighs 2 grams."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the northernmost Scandinavian country?",
        "answer": "Norway"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is sometimes called the `Land of Fire and Ice`?",
        "answer": "Iceland"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest of the Caribbean islands?",
        "answer": "Cuba"
    },
    {
        "question": "What area of the Atlantic is said to be responsible for the disappearance of ships and aircraft?",
        "answer": "Bermuda Triangle"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which was the first ocean to be crossed by ship and by plane?",
        "answer": "Atlantic Ocean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the only independent state smaller than Monaco?",
        "answer": "The Vatican"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Victoria Falls waterfall lies on the boundary of which two African countries?",
        "answer": "Zimbabwe and Zambia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which desert is found in South East Mongolia and Northern China?",
        "answer": "Gobi"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into which sea does the Nile river flow?",
        "answer": "The Mediterranean"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the longest river in the world?",
        "answer": "The Nile"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was Belize called until 1973?",
        "answer": "British Honduras"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country was the concentration camp `Treblinka` located?",
        "answer": "Poland"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the tallest mountain in the contiguous US?",
        "answer": "Mount Whitney"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Trinidad and Tobago?",
        "answer": "Port of Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "In the Western Hemisphere, what is the most western national capital?",
        "answer": "Mexico City"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which lake has the most fish species in the world?",
        "answer": "Lake Malawi - It is located in Africa between the countries Malawi, Mozambique and Tanzania."
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is the world`s largest supplier of olives?",
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "question": "Including underwater mountains, what is the longest mountain range on Earth?",
        "answer": "Ocean Ridge"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country is Thunder Bay?",
        "answer": "Canada "
    },
    {
        "question": "Thunder Bay is located in which country?",
        "answer": "Canada "
    },
    {
        "question": "What stretch of water lies between New Brunswick, Maine and Nova Scotia?",
        "answer": "Bay of Fundy"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Honduras?",
        "answer": "Tegucigalpa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Tegucigalpa is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Honduras"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which US state is Mount Vernon?",
        "answer": "Virginia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s notable about Yucat\u00e1n Peninsula lakes known as `cenotes`?",
        "answer": "They are underground"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows into the world`s largest waterfall?",
        "answer": "Zambezi River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which state`s name comes from the Chippewa word for `large lake`?",
        "answer": "Michigan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which capital name means `City of Joy`?",
        "answer": "Bucharest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city was the first capital of the United States?",
        "answer": "Philadelphia"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many U.S. states are called commonwealths?",
        "answer": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "What German city is famed for a scent it produces?",
        "answer": "Cologne"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the largest city in India?",
        "answer": "Mumbai"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the Guggenheim Museum?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fifth largest country in the world?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "What European capital celebrated its 2,000th anniversary in 1951?",
        "answer": "Paris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is bigger, the state of Florida or England?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the mythological birthplace of the Incas?",
        "answer": "Isla del Sol, Bolivia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. territory is the country`s southernmost point?",
        "answer": "American Samoa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which city served as the capital of West Germany?",
        "answer": "Bonn"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is home to the Spanish Steps?",
        "answer": "Rome, Italy"
    }
]